

Marco Gunawan

WEB DEVELOPER

- JI. KH Agus salim No. 71B Bekasi timur, Kota Bekasi
- mgunawan10@gmail.com
- □ 081947387912
- https://www.linkedin.com/ in/marco-gunawanb98761192/

PROFILE

A passionate professional in the field of information technology (IT), with a focus as a Front-End Developer. I am highly dedicated to creating attractive, responsive and functional web designs. I have an educational background in Informatics Engineering and work experience in managing production planning and stock control in manufacturing companies.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript

•••••

Problem Solving

•••••

PHP

•••••

C++

• • • • • •

WORK EXPERIENCE

PPIC STAFF

PT. Nijes Bayu Lestari

Jan 2021 - Present

- Controlling Stock materials
- Create planning production for future forecast
- Calculate work cost, transport cost, packing cost and apply it in the Quotation
- Emailing and Communicate with the supplier
- Create procedures based on SOP

ACCOUNTING STAFF

PT. Nijes Bayu Lestari

Jun 2018 - Des 2020

- Make Monthly income report
- · Make a monthly Cash flow report
- · Reporting monthly tax invoice
- Invoicing and mailing

EDUCATION HISTORY

Bachelor's degree of Information Technology

Mar 2018 - Jul 2023

Mercubuana University

- -Learning about algorithm
- -Learning about Machine learning
- -Able to understand programming language such as C++
- -Able to create my own mobile application

Senior High School (IPS)

Jun 2015 - Jun 2018

Nov 2022

Santa Maria Monica

CERTIFICATION

Arduino Programming and Hardware Fundamental

Udemy

ude.my/UC-05769b86-7c98-4f25-a5cf-9e1bab4657d4